ROSALYN LAND

roz.s.land@gmail.com

profile

A diligent and enthusiastic full-stack developer specialising in JavaScript, with a background in foreign languages. I have a common-sense approach to problem-solving, gained through experience working in a variety of roles. I am a fast learner and always keen to pick up new skills.

skills

Languages: JavaScript, Node.js

Testing: Mocha, Chai, Jest, Supertest **Back-end**: Express, Knex, PostgreSQL

Front-end: HTML5, CSS3, Adobe Illustrator and

Photoshop

Other: Git, GitHub, OOP, agile practices, CLI

Foreign languages: French, German

education and training

Deutsch Akademie, Hamburg, Germany

German Course
APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

German course level A2 to B2 according to the *CEFR*

Hamburg School of English, Hamburg, Germany

CELTA Course
APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

Qualification: CELTA Award, Pass

University of Manchester, Manchester, UK

French and Screen Studies
SEPTEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2015

Qualification: Bachelor of Arts (Honours), Upper

second-class (2:1)

experience

Northcoders Coding Bootcamp, Manchester, UK Student

JANUARY 2020 - APRIL 2020 (interrupted for lockdown period)

- Solid understanding of JavaScript full-stack development gained through daily problem-solving exercises, lectures and group work
- Implementation of agile practices, such as full test-driven-development and pair programming to deliver mini-projects to tight time-scales
- Competent use of the CLI for installing and managing software and version control

Goodgame Studios, Hamburg, Germany

Customer Services Representative

AUGUST 2018 - AUGUST 2019

- Liaised with customers and relayed their feedback to the development team in order to fix bugs and deploy new features in the games
- Regular 5-star ratings from customers, often with best average feedback score of the team

Self-employed, Hamburg, Germany

English as a Foreign Language Teacher

JANUARY 2016 - APRIL 2017

- Acquired good organisational skills through having to manage time between lesson planning, teaching and travelling
- Took initiative to create own lesson materials when they weren't available

DESY Housing Service, Hamburg, Germany *Web Intern*

web intern

AUGUST 2015 - NOVEMBER 2015

- Effective use of HTML, CSS and the company's Content Management System (CMS)
- Own initiative shown by issuing survey to website users in order to make improvements